Oh ephemeral soul
that lurks in the depths of deception,
who have you continued to wait for in the deserted woods?
Dispossessed of a wing,
the little bird closed its eyes in silence
The suffering has disappeared far away;
now the little bird does not cry anymore
A soft, silver mist
tenderly wraps up everything
Rest, rest in peace
In the story that I have written, you can fly in freedom
Here is my final incantation,
so that your light will know no shadow
So that the splendid golden dream will not be sullied
by the sadness brought about from the truth
Rest, rest in peace
In the story that I have written, you can fly in freedom
Here is my final incantation,
so that your light will know no shadow